KOSTAS NIKOU

DETAILS

ADDRESS

Limassol Cyprus

PHONE

96916096

EMAIL

nicoycostas@gmail.com

LINKS

https://costasnicou.com

www.linkedin.com/in/cnicou

SKILLS

Customer Service

Communication Skills

Ability to Work Under Pressure

Ability to Work in a Team

Technical Support

Microsoft 365

Active Directory

Wordpress Web Development

Linux System Administration

LANGUAGES

Greek

English

PROFILE

As an enthusiastic researcher and hands on learner during the last years, I have gained valuable experiences through studies and professional encounters. With an immense drive for success I am determined to build a great track record that will benefit any collaboration career path and organization.

EMPLOYMENT HISTORY

IT Technician / Junior Systems Engineer, Noteris Services Ltd

Limassol

Aug 2023 — Present

- Serve as the first contact with company users who need technical assistance via the phone, email or ticketing system.
- Troubleshoot, diagnose, and resolve technical hardware and/or software issues
- · Provide quick resolution and excellent customer service
- · Redirect unresolved issues to the next level of support personnel
- · On boarding and off boarding of users
- Microsoft 365 & Exchange Online Administration (User Creation, Mailbox conversion, Email Delegation)

NOC Analyst, Equiti

Limassol

Nov 2022 — Mar 2023

- Incident handling, escalation, reporting, tracking issues, troubleshooting problems
- · Network support for internal security investigation
- · Equiti Global Network Monitoring
- · Cloud infrastructure deployment AWS, Azure, Microsoft Office 365.

IT Support Engineer, Primetel

Limassol

Sep 2021 — Sep 2022

Responsible for the installation, operation and maintenance of computer systems by providing key system and network administration. Troubleshooting and diagnosing of hardware and software issues over a remote connection or either in person

EDUCATION

HOBBIES

Listening and Writing Rap Music, Reading Personal Development Books, Front End Web Development

BSc Hons Computing, Edinburgh Napier University

2016 — 2020

Modules: (Cisco CCNA Routing and Switching, Linux Network services (Centos - Red Hat), Vyatta Firewall. Bash scripting, IT Service Management ITIL, Information Systems Project Management (PRINCE2), PHP, JQuery, MySQL, Python, Advanced Web Technologies with Python Flask

Information Technology Diploma, Cyprus College

2013 - 2015

Modules: Windows Server Administration, Hardware and software troubleshooting

CCNA Discovery networking for home and small businesses. Introduction to Cybersecurity,

COURSES

Red Hat Certified System Administrator (RHCSA) RHEL 9, Red Hat

Apr 2024

MS-102 Microsoft 365 Administrator, Udemy Nov 2023

Active Directory & Group Policy Lab, Udemy Jul 2023

Edinburgh